<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- TEMPERATURE -->
    <string name="glossary_temperature_title">TEMPERATURE</string>
    <string name="glossary_temperature_description" formatted="false">A temperature is a comparative objective measure of hot and cold.         It is measured, typically by a thermometer, through the bulk behavior         of a thermometric material, detection of heat radiation, or by particle         velocity or kinetic energy. It may be calibrated in any of various         temperature scales, Celsius, Fahrenheit, Kelvin, etc.          Temperature is important in all fields of natural science,         including physics, geology, chemistry, atmospheric sciences and biology.</string>

    <!-- HUMIDITY -->
    <string name="glossary_humidity_title">HUMIDITY</string>
    <string name="glossary_humidity_description" formatted="false">Humidity is the amount of water vapor in the air.         Water vapor is the gaseous state of water and is invisible. Humidity indicates the likelihood         of precipitation, dew, or fog. Higher humidity reduces the effectiveness of sweating in cooling         the body by reducing the rate of evaporation of moisture from the skin.</string>

    <!-- DEW POINT -->
    <string name="glossary_dewpoint_title">DEW POINT</string>
    <string name="glossary_dewpoint_description" formatted="false">The dew point is the temperature at which the water vapor         in air at constant barometric pressure condenses into liquid         water at the same rate at which it evaporates.         At temperatures below the dew point, water will leave the air.</string>

    <!-- HEAT INDEX -->
    <string name="glossary_heatindex_title">HEAT INDEX</string>
    <string name="glossary_heatindex_description" formatted="false">The heat index (HI) or humiture or humidex (not to be confused with the Canadian humidex)         is an index that combines air temperature and relative humidity in an attempt to determine         the human-perceived equivalent temperature—how hot it feels. The result is also known as         the \"felt air temperature\" or \"apparent temperature\". For example, when the temperature         is 32 °C (90 °F) with very high humidity, the heat index can be about 41 °C (106 °F)         The human body normally cools itself by perspiration, or sweating. Heat is removed from         the body by evaporation of that sweat. However, relative humidity reduces the evaporation         rate because the higher vapor content of the surrounding air does not allow the maximum         amount of evaporation from the body to occur. This results in a lower rate of heat removal         from the body, hence the sensation of being overheated. This effect is subjective; its         measurement has been based on subjective descriptions of how hot subjects feel for a         given temperature and humidity. This results in a heat index that relates one         combination of temperature and humidity to another.</string>

    <!-- SOURCE -->
    <string name="glossary_source">Source: Wikipedia.org</string>
</resources>
